In this short video, we're gonna take a look at interfaces in Java. Interfaces
在这段简短的视频中，我们将看看Java中的接口。接口
specify relationships between classes without using inheritance. So, here is an
在不使用继承的情况下指定类之间的关系。所以，这里有一个
example: uh, we have an interface here called the point interface. And a point
示例：嗯，我们这里有一个接口，称为点接口。还有一点
interface can have a, a bunch of methods in it, and, and we just declare the, the
接口中可以有一个、一组方法，我们只需声明
signature of those methods. You can also have other things besides methods, but uh,
这些方法的签名。除了方法你还可以有其他的东西，但是呢，
the main thing that uh, they're used for usually is for a, a method interface. So
这个通常主要是用来做一个，一个方法接口。所以
uh, here's an example of a particular method, the move method, and it takes some
嗯，这里有一个特殊方法的例子，移动方法，它需要一些
arguments and has a particular return type. Now any other class, or any class,
参数，并具有特定的返回类型。现在任何其他的班级，或者任何班级，
excuse me, that's going to implement the point interface has to provide a method
打扰一下，要实现的Point接口必须提供一个方法
uh, with the same signature. So, if this, see because the point interface has a move
呃，签名是一样的。因此，如果出现这种情况，请参见，因为点界面有一个移动
method, the. A class will have to have a move method with the same signature, as
方法的基础上，提出了一种基于。类必须具有具有相同签名的Move方法，如下所示
the move method in the declared interface. And if the point interface had other
声明的接口中的Move方法。如果该点接口具有其他
methods ah, then the point class would also have to implement those methods by,
方法啊，那么Point类也必须通过，
you know having a method of the same name ah, with the appropriate types of
你知道有一个同名的方法啊，有合适的类型的
arguments and result. Now it says in the Java language manual that Java programs
论据和结果。现在它在Java语言手册中说Java程序
can use interfaces to make it unnecessary for related classes to share a common
可以使用接口使相关类不必共享共同的
abstract super class or to add methods to objects. And the translation of that is
抽象超类或向对象添加方法。这句话的翻译是
that interfaces play the same role as multiple inheritance in c plus, plus. So
这些接口在c++中扮演着与多重继承相同的角色。所以
interfaces uh, are really analogous uh, to, to multiple inheritance. And the
接口呢，真的是类似于呃，类似于多重继承。以及
reason for that, is that, a, a class can implement multiple interfaces. So, if I
原因是，第一，一个类可以实现多个接口。所以，如果我
have a class x and it implements a three interfaces a, b, and c. This means an
有一个类x，它实现了三个接口a、b和c。
extra object can be treated as an A object or B object or a C object in the
额外的对象可以作为A对象、B对象或C对象在
appropriate context. So it's like or almost as if X has three superclasses A, B
适当的上下文。所以它就像或者几乎就像X有三个超类A，B
and C. Now uh, there are some important differences uh, but there is the effect,
和C现在呢有一些重要的区别呢，但是有效果，
and so if I wanted to have a class that gets functionality or implements a
因此，如果我希望拥有一个获取功能的类或实现
functionality uh, several uh, uh, interfaces that's, I mean we do very
功能性呃，几个呃，呃，接口，我的意思是我们非常
directly in java just by saying if the classes going to implement all those
直接用java编写，只需说明类是否要实现所有这些
interfaces. >> Now here is an example of an application of that, so think about a
接口。>>现在这是一个应用程序的示例，所以请考虑一下
graduate student ah, working at Stanford or some other university, so ah, typically
研究生啊，在斯坦福或者其他的大学工作，所以啊，典型的
graduate students are students, okay they take classes and have property's that
研究生就是学生，好吧，他们上课，而且有财产
students ah, have they get degrees and grades and things like that. >> Graduate
学生啊，有没有拿到学位，拿到等级之类的东西。>>研究生
students also work for the University? >> They are often teaching assistants in
学生也在大学工作？>他们经常是学校的助教。
classes or research assistant [inaudible] so there [inaudible] another role which is
课堂或研究助理[听不见]所以还有另一个角色[听不见]是
university employee, and if I have gone to ah, trouble ah, in my. I, university
大学职员，如果我去了啊，麻烦啊，在我的。我，大学
personnel management software to implement functionality to deal with students and to
人事管理软件，实现处理学生和
implement functionality to deal with employees. Well, then I would like to make
实现与员工打交道的功能。好的，那么我想做一个
use of that when I get around to thinking about how I'm going to implement uh, the
当我考虑我要如何实现，嗯，这一点的时候，我就会用到这一点
functionality for graduate students and one way to do that. Would be if I had a
为研究生提供的功能，以及实现这一功能的一种方法。如果我有一个
class with implement, if I had, excuse me, an interface for employees and interface
带工具的类，如果我有一个员工接口和接口的话
for student, and I would say that graduate student could be both, okay. So a graduate
对于学生来说，我想说研究生可以两者兼而有之，好吧。所以一个毕业生
student can implement both the employee interface and student interface. And, and
学生可以实现员工界面和学生界面。还有，还有
the reason that's this is a good idea, is it is actually hard to do this if ah, you
之所以说这是个好主意，是因为如果啊，你这么做其实很难
only have single inheritance. If you think about it, if I had set things up so that I
只有一个继承人。如果你想一想，如果我设置了一些东西，这样我就可以
had some employee classes and some student classes and now I want to make graduate
上过一些员工班和学生班，现在我想毕业了
students. Well now what am I going to do? Well if I have my employee class. I can
学生们。那么现在我该怎么办呢？如果我有员工班的话。我可以的
make grad students a subclass of that but now how do I get the student functionality
使研究生成为其中的一个子类，但是现在我如何获得学生功能呢？
and similarly. If I have a student class, I can make graduate student a subclass of
同样的，也是如此。如果我有一个学生班，我可以让研究生成为
that. But now, how do I get the employee functionality? So in single inheritance,
那。但是现在，我如何获得员工功能呢？所以在单一继承中，
you're forced to choose a single class to inherit from. And the advantage of
您必须选择一个要继承的类。它的优点是
interfaces is that it will let you get functionality or implement functionality,
接口是它将让您获得功能或实现功能，
or express the relationship, at least, of functionality to multiple kinds of things.
或者至少表达功能与多种事物的关系。
And so I can have one, uh, graduate student class that implements both the
所以我可以有一个，呃，研究生班级，它实现了
employee and the student functionality. So how are interfaces different from
员工和学生功能。那么，接口与
inheritance? Well, probably the biggest difference is that it's not possible to
继承？那么可能最大的区别就是不可能
implement interfaces as efficiently as inheritance. And that's why you have both.
实现接口与继承一样高效。这就是为什么你两者都有的原因。
So you'd prefer to use inheritance, uh, if you can, because it's going to be more
所以你更愿意使用继承，呃，如果你可以的话，因为它将会有更多的
efficient than interfaces. And what makes interfaces less efficient? Well, the
比接口更高效。是什么降低了接口的效率？那么，这个
primary thing. Is that if the class is implementing interfaces need not be at
主要的事情。是如果类正在实现接口，则不需要在
fixed offsets. In fact, we will not be able, in general, uh, to assign methods in
固定偏移。实际上，我们一般不能，呃，把方法赋给
interfaces to fixed offsets inside of a class implementation or an object
与类实现或对象内部的固定偏移量的接口
implementation. So let's take a look at an example. Here's our point interface again.
实施。那么让我们来看一个例子。这又是我们的点界面。
Now say we have one class point when we saw this one before [inaudible]. And it
现在假设我们在之前看到这个时有一个班级点数[听不见]。而且它
implements the move method has to implement the move method. And then we
实现Move方法必须实现Move方法。然后我们
have another class that also points to point interface but it also implements
我有另一个类，它也指向点接口，但它也实现了
some other stuff. Okay so, it might implement some other methods that aren't
一些其他的东西。好的，因此，它可能会实现一些其他未实现的方法
part of that interface. So now how would we decide you know, where to put the move
界面的一部分。那么现在我们将如何决定，你知道，把搬家的地点放在哪里呢？
method. Well the natural thing, that, that we've discussed. [inaudible] Say of course
方法。这是我们讨论过的自然而然的事情。[听不见]当然可以说
[inaudible] is that the methods ah, would be laid out in the order in which they are
[听不见]就是这些方法啊，会按照它们的顺序来排列
declared, so if we did that clearly the move method will not be ah, in the first
声明了，所以如果我们这样做的话，清楚的移动方法将不会是啊，在第一个
position in both of these classes. Now. We could imagine, uh, a separate compiler
在这两个类中都有位置。现在。我们可以想象，呃，一个单独的编译器
pass, that we're trying to sort the methods. So that, say, all the methods of
通过，我们正在尝试对方法进行排序。所以，比方说，所有的方法
the point interface always appeared in the same position and in the same order in any
点界面始终以相同的位置和顺序出现在任何
class, implements the point interface. But that doesn't work as soon as we have, um,
类，实现Point接口。但那不会在我们有，嗯，
multiple interfaces being implemented. So let's say that the point two class here
正在实施多个接口。所以我们假设这里的第二节课
implemented another interface A. So, how can we then implement interfaces? Well,
实现了另一个接口A。那么，我们如何实现接口呢？井,
so, it's going to be a little more complex than usual to implement in this batch, say
所以，比方说，在这一批中实现它将比通常情况下稍微复杂一些
to a method f, where e has some interface type. So if e is typed as having some
方法f，其中e具有某种接口类型。所以如果e类型为有一些
interface and now we're calling it the f method of that interface, then we're going
接口，现在我们将其称为该接口的f方法，然后
to have to do a little bit more work. And so here's one approach, this approach is
不得不多做一点工作。所以这里有一种方法，这种方法是
actually quite inefficient, but you will see that it will work. And there are other
实际上效率很低，但你会看到它会奏效的。还有其他的
approaches that are more efficient, but that's not particularly important, so
更有效的方法，但这并不是特别重要，所以
here's one way that can work. So each class of implements interface is going to
这里有一种方法可以奏效。所以每一类实现接口都将
have a look-up table associated with it that maps method names, the string names
有一个与其相关联的查找表，该表映射方法名称、字符串名称
of methods, to those methods themselves. And then. Uh, we can hash the method names
这些方法本身。然后。呃，我们可以散列这些方法的名称
for faster look-up and we can actually compute. Uh, those hashes at compile time.
为了更快的查找，我们实际上可以进行计算。呃，编译时的那些散列。
And so the idea would be that if when we have an object. Ah, somewhere in the
所以我们的想法是，如果我们有一个物体。啊，在这里的某个地方
object, probably at the dispatch pointer. The dispatch pointer you know will point
对象，可能位于调度指针。您知道的调度指针将指向
off to a list of methods, sort of the normal methods of the class. But somewhere
方法列表，类的常规方法。但是在某个地方
say maybe at the end of the dispatch table there will be another pointer to some kind
假设在分派表的末尾可能会有另一个指向某种类型的指针
of look up table that maps names. Two, two methods to quote. Okay. So, somehow
映射名称的查找表。两种，两种方式来引用。好吧。所以，不知何故
associated with every object of every class ah, we will have this look up table
关联到每个类的每一个对象啊，我们都会有这个查询表
that will map ah, the, the names of interface methods to the actual codes for
这将把啊，接口方法的名称映射到
those methods that influence them. All right and we'd already decided uh, that
那些影响他们的方法。好的，我们已经决定了，呃，那
the, for the point interface that the move method should go first. It should be the
对于点界面，应首先执行Move方法。它应该是
first method in the class. Well, if we had made a similar decision for the a
类中的第一个方法。嗯，如果我们对a做了类似的决定
interface, some method in that interface that should always be listed first in the
接口，接口中某些方法应该始终列在
give to all the methods and all the interfaces so that they can be maintained
提供给所有方法和所有接口，以便它们可以维护
across all of the uh, classes that implement those interfaces. At least
所有实现这些接口的呃类。至少
classes that are declared and all the interfaces that are declared. And that's
声明的类和所有声明的接口。那就是
kind of un-Java. And that we don't want to uh, force people to declare all the
有点不像Java。我们不想，呃，强迫人们申报所有
classes and the interfaces once and not be able to extend them in the future. Alright
类和接口只有一次，以后就不能扩展了。好的，好的
so the bottom line is that methods in interfaces do not live at fixed process in
因此，底线是接口中的方法不存在于